ELVIS IAN OMONDI

What is provided here is all true and genuine.

Curriculum vitae

Elvis ian omondi

E|O

ELVIS IAN OMONDI

------ FULL STACK DEVELOPER AND MARKETING ASSOCIATE ------

Address: Busia, Kenya.

Phone: +254703180147

elvisianomondi@gmail.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

To be a globally competitive professional with a vast knowledge and experience in Information Communication Technology Management under software development and marketing. I advocate for the best practices and governance in provision of amicable solution to current humanity challenges.

CORE OUALIFICATIONS

- Strong experience in computer programming using Python, Java, PHP, Javascript, Html and NodeJS.
- software developer, databases designing, ICT consultancy,
- Skills in Excel, MS Word, PowerPoint, Adobe and spreadsheet, Adobe photo shop.
- Well-developed understanding of contemporary project.
- Excellent written and verbal communication skills developed,
- Taking responsibility for individual contributions and collaborating with others through community involvement.
- Modifying, testing, verifying and analyzing information and data.
- Client Advocacy.
- Capacity building and empowerment.

Academic Qualification

- 2016-2020:Maseno University (B.sc Information, communication, technology with management(ICTM))
- 2012-2015: certificate for complication of secondary school (K.C.S.E)
- 20002-2011: Primary School certificate(KCPE)

Other professional trainings

- 2012: Certificate in Leadership and Management
- 2011: Certificate of Mentorship

Responsibilities

- Provide a variety of application using technology and communicate effectively with technical users and non-technical users.
- Observe and evaluate computer performance and development, troubleshooting, repairing system problems.
- software profiency ensuring enough security in the computer system to prevent important institution documents cannot be leaked
- Maintain operating system, application software and provide appropriate report of the state of the system.
- Help users and provide help-desk support and problem tracking system to answer user questions.
- maintain accurate, update and complete records of progress and development in a sector
- Update system software accurately and completely as per required by the developer.
- Follow required policies on what is required in the organization or institution to have to ensure effectiveness working environment.

Key Competencies

- God, Self-motivation and high level energy
- verbal and written communication skills
- attention to detail and shown high working standards
- problem solving and decision making

- organizing and planning
- work under pressure
- learning orientation
- critical thinking
- flexibility and adaptability

Experience

2019-4 to 2019-8: Industrial Attachment at City Campus.

Duties: Technical support under communication technology like networking and software development.

2020-4 to 2020-7: Did Digital sales and marketing for monarch insurance company, selling of company policies online.

2021-2 to 2021-5: Worked with collection Africa as customer care service, managing various accounts of individuals with debts.

REFEREES

Prof.F. Makoyo

Dean of Studies

Lecturer, Maseno University

Profmakoyo@gmail.com

Idah Achieng

Department of computing and informatics

Admin , Maseno University

Phone number: 0710324716

Emily Atieno Okembo

Administrator Maseno University

eokembo@yahoo.com

phone: 0704300783